AMIT VERMA

Frontend Developer

- **\$655568110**
- @ amitverma951994@gmail.com
- Kurla West, Mumbai

EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer

Robinhood Insurance Pvt Ltd

math 23-Jan-2018 to till date. Vikhroli West, Mumbai

Oneinsure OneGo

- The OneGo app is a unique platform that makes selling insurance a matter of a few taps on your phone screen.
- This app is developed on Ionic 3 framework

Oneinsure App

- . The OneInsure app lets you digitally store all your insurance policies and avail various services and support on them for a lifetime.
- This app is developed on Ionic 3 framework

Oneinsure SalesApp

- · This app is primarily useful for Sales & Upsell Teams to create to do list, understand client requirements, store client details, and monitor& manage daily/weekly/yearly tasks at various levels.
- This app is developed on Ionic 1 framework

Chat Application

- This app is bascially useful to communicate between teams and also use for support base.
- This app is developed on Firebase and Ionic 3 Framework

Oneinsure Portal

- Oneinsure portal is a web version where we can view policy and buy them.
- Oneinsure portal is developed on Angular Js

SMS Application

- This app is used to send auto sms from user device and it's mainly developed for Tellicallers Leads.
- This app is developed on Ionic 3 Framework

Senior Frontend Developer

Travelibro Pvt Ltd

iii 1-Aug-2016 to 16-Jan-2018

Mumbai Central - Tardeo, Mumbai

TraveLibro Website

· Travelibro is a social network where we can checkin and upload feeds and store our photos and videos.

SUMMARY

Total work experience as a Software Developer is 4 years and 2 months in developing Websites, Hyrbid Applications.

1 years of experience on Ionic 3 Framework.

Technologies and Libraries hands on are Ionic 1, Ionic 3, Angular Js, Angular 5, Html5, Css3, Sass, Less, Graphql, Javascript, Jquery, Parcel Js as a build tool.

TECHNOLOGIES

Coding

Open Project

Bootstrap Javascript Jquery Ionic 1 Ionic 2 and 3 Framework Angular Js Angular 5 GraphQL
Angular Js Angular 5 GraphQL
Version Control GitHub SVN Bitbucket

Wohlig Technology

· Wohlig is catalyst that transforms the clients perspective of technology and

- empowers them to take advantage of the digital revolution that is constantly evolving.

EXPERIENCE

Web developer

math in the second second in the second in t

- Wohlig technology is a service based company.

PASSIONS

Dancing			
Rapping	 	 	
Cricket		 	

EDUCATION

BSC-IT

KJ Somaiya Sci and Comm

iii 2013 - 2015 Vidyavihar, Mumbai